psychological 9407 wrote for returning a birthday gift I got for my boyfriend after he insulted me about my colourful past
this happened last night but my phone is still blowing up I have 26
dipped into my savings and got Mike my boyfriend 27 A PS5 for his birthday yesterday
he knew he was getting the PS5 because he told me that the PS5 is the only thing he wants
we've been together for 4 years so the cost didn't matter that is until I found out what he thinks about me
some background when I was 18 I was involved with Jake a guy who I met online
we ended things after 3 months and I moved on shortly after without him a guy from work
I found out a couple months later that Jake and Adam were actually really close friends but I didn't know Jake long enough to meet his friend group so I had no idea
after finding out I took some time off dating in two years later I met my current boyfriend Mike
I was upfront and honest with Mike about my past in the fact that I was unintentionally involved with friends
he said he understood in my past didn't bother him last night at his party I showed up with a PS5 and him and his friends were screaming with joy
is best female friend Jessica laughed and said I wish I was a thought so I could afford a ps52
I looked at her with an excuse me look on my face and she just said nevermind and walked away
I confronted my boyfriend about it and he said and I quote she's just messing with you you can't take a joke
so I pushed further as to why this girl is even calling me names to begin with and he said well everyone knows you were thought before you met me
I asked him to explain how I was a thought before him and he said you know messing with best friends
didn't put me on the shoulder and said that it's okay because I'm not who I was back then and if he could get over my colourful past and thought mentalities to give me a chance
then I could get over Jessica's comments and give her another chance I didn't say anything
I just got up took the PS5 from the gift table and left
pissed he literally called me like 20 times but I didn't care I was so hurt that I took the Bell off and took it straight back to the store I got it from
they heavily refunded it I thought that was done but Mike and all his friends including Jessica arbitrating me for being petty and they're all saying I brought this on myself by making poor choices
I responded to Mike and told him that he deserves better than me so find someone who wasn't a thought and get the PS5 from them because I returned it
he started screaming how I'm the biggest off for returning it and how I should be happy he ignored my colourful past
I'm thinking maybe taking it back went too far am I the a-hole sweet potato famished Road
I'm so confused but maybe that's because I'm an old lady who got married around the time you were in kindergarten
if anyone was wrong in the Jake's Ottomans and it was Adam you might have dated friend
but he dated his best friend's ex that's on them to figure out an atom's mistake only
to where I come from dating three dudes and 7 years does not a colourful past make
did Hulk get a new definition since the early 00s not the a-hole
and I hope you do something special for yourself with a little of that money you got back from returning the gift you got your ex-boyfriend
190 pairs of panties Road and ta give him the keys to the curb
also dollars to dildos he's cheating with Jessica deleted wrote removed